Thank you for watching.
[ED
Please subscribe to our channel!
How to spend after-school Lalaport in Lalaport Yokohama
Hello everyone. I am Nakano-jin, the principal of Lalaport Yokohama Nakano.
This is Higuchi, also a Nakano-jin.
This time, we are going to have a special summer vacation lesson,
We will focus on entertainment, food, and various information that will make you want to come here during your summer vacation.
We will be sending you information from Raraport Yokohama.
Raraport Yokohama is a 7-minute walk from Kamoi Station on the JR Yokohama Line,
Ito-Yokohama Road, which reopened in April, trendy fast-fashion stores, and the 13-screen Dongfang Cinema,
Ito-Yokohama Road, which was renovated in April, trendy fast fashion, and the 13-screen Higashikata Cinemas,
There are approximately 270 stores to meet a wide range of needs and wants.
Two special students who came to take a special summer vacation class are these two. Go ahead.
Everyone, lock on to your hearts!
We are the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department.
Yes, I'm Hitoko Nagakawa, aka Hito-chan, the super-tokimeki red.
Yes, I'm Aki Suda, aka Aki-chan, the Super HotMe Lemon.
Yes, I'm Aki Suda, aka Aki-chan of Super Hot Mood Lemon.
Today, I'm going to show you the charms of Raraport Yokohama that you don't know yet, so please look forward to it.
Let's start the summer vacation special class "Super Tokimeki Raraport Yokohama Tour!
So, the first stop is an entertainment spot recommended by my principal!
It's at the Toylo Park Powered by Little Planet!
Looks like a lot of fun!
This is a next generation theme park where play turns into learning!
There are digital trampolines, AR snarls, and many other futuristic activities.
You can play to your heart's content even on a rainy day!
And here is Mr. Suzuki, the special lecturer who will be introducing us.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Mr. Suzuki, nice to meet you.
This attraction is a fusion of video and trampoline.
It was very difficult.
Cough, cough!
In the end...
So, how did you two like the first class?
It was fun. I thought it was great that we could move our bodies so much indoors.It was fun. I thought it was great that we could move our bodies so much indoors.
Since you two were able to have fun today, I am sure the other guests will be able to have even more fun, so thank you very much.
Let's go to the next class.
Okay, let's go to the next class.
Next, for the second period, I would like to recommend an entertainment spot.
It is the Touhou Cinemas Raraport Yokohama.
Wow, you can already see how big it is.
It doesn't feel too much like a cannon.
This is the fifth location in Japan to use the iMAX Digital Sharpener,
This is the fifth cinema in Japan to use the iMAX Digital Sharpener, which allows you to experience the latest technology and feel as if you are in the middle of a movie.
There is also a wide variety of food, an indispensable part of the movie experience.
Wow, this is amazing.
This is so rainbow.
Look, there is a camera.
It's so cute.
Are they strawberries?
It's amazing how crispy it is for popcorn.
Tasteful, delicious.
Strawberry mais!
Pink!
Crunchy!
Cute and tasty!
Great!
To go with the movie!
Let's go to the next class!
Yes!
The third restaurant is a food spot recommended by my principal!
The Buffet Po-Po-Ten Sing!
Yay!
This is an all-you-can-eat restaurant where you can enjoy the gourmet food of Taiwan, the land of the fallen.
It is an all-you-can-eat restaurant!
And here is our special lecturer, Mr. Rachi!
I'm Rachi, a member of our staff. Please give me a warm welcome!
Please give me a warm welcome!
What is the system here?
A la carte dishes such as hot tempsin like xiaolongbao, ramen noodles, hot and cold vegetables, etc.Hot tenshin such as xiaolongbao, ramen noodles, hot and cold vegetables, and other a la carte dishes
You can enjoy as much as you like in a buffet style!
What is the most popular item on the menu?
The hot xiaolongbao with its glutinous skin and juicy filling!
I want to eat it! Delicious!
Delicious!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm going to eat it!
I can't wait!
Delicious! Doughy!
Oh!
Yum!
How's the authentic Chinese taste?
It's a little bit of everything.
So you get to try a lot of different dishes.
Everything was delicious.
I'm sure I could go on and on.
But I think it's time to move on to the next class.
The fourth game is for me!
Kyoto's recommended food spot!
Mother Farm Cafe & Soft Ice Cream!
This is a directly managed store of Mother Farm!
We have a wide variety of fresh dairy products including thick soft-serve ice cream made from freshly squeezed milk.
and a wide variety of fresh dairy products!
For you and your partner
This is a Yokohama limited edition
Waffle Ball Cassis Berry & Peach and
and a summer-only version of our most popular item.
Café Soft Tropical Man
Cafe Soft Tropical Man.
Yes!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Wow!
The soft serve ice cream is so rich!
and the slightly refreshing mango sauce matches it perfectly!The mango sauce is delicious, and the mango sauce is a bit refreshing.
I'll have another bowl!
So sweet!
Delicious!
It's so sweet and delicious!
What do you think? How does it taste?
It's so good!
So much fruit on top of such a luxurious fruit!
The milk is so rich, I couldn't get enough!
Now that you've had your fill, let's move on to the next class!
Yes! Let's go!
The fifth place is recommended by the principal!
This is HMV Raraport Yokohama!
This store boasts a stylish interior and offers a wide selection of CDs, DVDs, Blu-rays, books, and accessories.
And here is Mr. Sekiyama, the special lecturer who will be introducing us. Please give him my best regards.
I am Sekiyama, a staff member of HMV Raraport Yokohama. Pleased to meet you.
What kind of music and genres are popular among Generation Z now?
K-pop continues to be popular, and new artists are debuting all the time,
Young artists...
Now, Mr. Sekiyama, please give us a tour of the store.
Please do. Let's go.
It's hard to choose, isn't it, since the selection is so large that it's hard to believe it's a CD store.
There were so many.
But I found the item I wanted the most.
Here it is.
Our photo book!
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. Actually, I found the item I want most, too.
It's this way.
It's our CD.
And a lot of ska.
What kind of music is on this CD?
Se-no!
Give me Love, or I won't.
Please spoil me more!
Don't be nice to me, don't be nice to meDon't ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever.
Just look at me.
To be continued.
Thank you very much.
Now I would like to go to the last spot.
Thank you very much for your teacher, Sekima.
Thank you very much.
And for the last 6th period, Kyoto is the recommended spot.
This is Suzunoya.
This store has been established in the hope that people all over Japan will know the joy of wearing kimono.
This store offers a wide variety of beautiful kimonos and kimonos that are easy to wear.
We hope you will feel the summer spirit here.
We would like you to choose a yukata that you and your partner would like to wear this summer.
Yay!
What are the trendy yukata of the season?
Nuanced colors like this are the trend.
Dusky pink and grayish shades are especially popular.
Are there any fashionable ways to wear yukata?
The trend is to coordinate with a single tone without using accent colors.
So, with the above in mind, let's choose the yukata we want to wear this summer.
Yay!
Please subscribe to our channel.
Now, let's take a look at Sakai-san's yukata coordination. Go ahead!
Next, let's take a look at Suda-san's yukata coordinate. Here you go!
Both of you are so cute!
You are so cute!
Thank you very much.
Since we're here, let's go for a walk.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Now, as a special summer vacation class, we're going to have a special class on entertainment food recommended by Raraport Yokohama, and we'd like you to experience it while learning about it.
How did you both enjoy the experience while learning with Mr. Sakai and Ms. Suda?
I was able to enjoy all the fun things to the fullest just at this LaLaport Yokohama, and I thought the day was very fulfilling.
There were many people from all walks of life playing games, eating food, wearing yukata, eating ice cream, and so on.
I hope many people will enjoy playing games, eating food, wearing yukata (light cotton kimono), eating ice cream, and having fun!
What is the degree of excitement of this special tour of Raraport Yokohama?What is the degree of your crush for this special class of the Lalaport Yokohama Special Tour?
This time's crush level is Heartlactic Lactic Lactic Tea!
Thank you very much!
There are many more recommended spots in Raraport Yokohama that we have not been able to introduce to you!
And at Raraport Yokohama, we are offering a limited time offer of the couple's autographs!
In addition, the yukata that the two of you are wearing will also be on display!
We also appear on the signage and make announcements in the museum.
If you find this video interesting, please subscribe to our channel by clicking the "Good Button"!
Thank you very much for watching!
Thank you very much.
Mitsui Fudosan Group